You know who it is, coming 'round again
You want a dose of this right now
It's KDA, uh!
I'm a goddess with a blade
소리쳐 봐 내 이름 잊지 못하게 loud, loud, loud, loud
I could take it to the top 절대 멈추지 못해
내가 끝내주는 bad gal, gal, gal
And when I start to talk like that (like that)
Oh, you won't know how to react
I'm a picture perfect face, with that wild in my veins
You can hear it in my growl, growl, growl, growl
So keep your eyes on me now
무엇을 보든 좋아할 거야
닿을 수 없는 level
나와 대결 원한 널 확신해
We got it all in our hands now
So can you handle what we're all about?
We're so tough (tough), not scared to show you up (up)
Can you feel the rush now?
Ain't nobody bringing us down, down, down, down, down, down
They could try but we're gonna wear the crown
You could go another round
Round, round, round, round, round, round
Wish you luck, but you're not bringing us down
We go hard, 'til we get it, get it
We go hard, we so in it, in it
We Pop Stars (Pop Stars), only winning, winning now
Ain't nobody bringing us down, down, down, down
Hey! You ready for this? (Let's go!)
See 언제든지 내 모습 magic
단 한 번에 내가 잡어 절대 기죽지 않지, uh!
Pow-pow 네가 뭘 알아 (알아)
견딜 수 없어, 원해도 (해도)
원하는 게 얼굴에 보여
I'm trouble and you're wanting it
I'm so cold (so cold)
When I move that way, you gonna be so blown (so blown)
I'm the realest in the game, uh!
Say I'm on fire with a blade
You're about to hear my name
Ringing in your head like, oh...
So keep your eyes on me now
무엇을 보든 좋아할 거야
We're so tough (tough), not scared to show you up (up)
Can you feel the rush now?
Ain't nobody bringing us down, down, down, down, down, down
They could try but we're gonna wear the crown
You could go another round
Round, round, round, round, round, round
Wish you luck, but you're not bringing us down
We go hard, 'til we get it, get it
We go hard, we so in it, in it
We Pop Stars (Pop Stars), only winning, winning now
Ain't nobody bringing us down, down, down, down
Hhmmm... hhmmm...
Oh, 난 멈추지 않아
Oh, oh, we go hard
Oh, oh, we Pop Stars (stars), stars (stars)
Ain't nobody bringing us-
Ain't nobody bringing us down, down, down, down, down, down
They could try but we're gonna wear the crown
You could go another round
Round, round, round, round, round, round
Wish you luck, but you're not bringing us down
We go hard, 'til we get it, get it
We go hard, we so in it, in it
We Pop Stars (Pop Stars), only winning, winning now
Ain't nobody bringing us down, down, down, down